MUHAMMED FURQAN **AHMFD**

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+91 9650807962

New Delhi, India

furqanahmedmj@gmail.com

lin Linkedln

 \bigcirc GitHub

Muhammed Furgan Ahmed

EDUCATION

HIGHER SECONDARY - HUMANITIES Kendriye Vidyalaya Andrews Gani

Mar 2014 - Apr 2016

BACHELOR OF ARTS Delhi University

Aug 2017 - 2021

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

- Critical Thinking
- · Time Management
- Leadership

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- · React.is
- Angular.js
- Node.js
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Redux

SUMMARY

A full stack web developer with a passion for creating beautiful, functional websites. The expertise lies in HTML, CSS, Javascript, React and Node.js. Has a keen eye for detail and takes great pride in the work. Enjoys working on creative projects and pushing the boundaries of what is possible. Always striving to learn new things and to further the development skills.

<u>PROJECTS</u>

Sephora Clone



Easy, Fast And Secure Shopping website where user find new fashion based branded clothes in cheap prices!

Features

- User Authentication and Admin Page
- Checkout, Cart, OTP Pages (CRUD operation)
- Similar UI
- Fully Responsive

Tech Stack: React, Redux, React-router-dom, Bootstrap, Styled Chakra

EXPERIENCE

As a Front-End Developer/ Deputy Administration head at United for Humanity (NGO)

JAN 2020 - MAR 2022

- Developed captivating UI/UX design concepts for the website.
- Created responsive website designs for cross-browser compatibility.
- Collaborated with back-end developers to integrate the design with the backend system.
- Implemented branding strategies for organization campaigns.
- Designed promotional materials and visuals for fundraising activities.
- · Managed a team of 3 graphic designers to maintain design consistency.
- Oversaw website design maintenance for optimal user engagement.

IT & DESIGN TEAM | LIBERTE MUN

JAN 2019 - JAN 2020

- · Refreshed the website's frontend
- Assisted in establishing and managing the backend infrastructure
- · Created promotional materials and visuals for fundraising initiatives.